Previously on
Two and a Half Men...
Excuse me, do you know
the difference
between "organic beef"
and "grass-fed beef"?
She was totally hitting on you.
You should ask her out.
Hey, Zoey, you want
to on a date with me?!
Sure!
When I was in high school,
I met this girl named Bridget.
You're still in love
with her, aren't you?
See, look. No wedding ring.
Hmm, I noticed
the bright white tan line.
No worries. I gave it to Alan.
Oh... very valuable.
You seem like
a really sweet guy,
but I think you're still kind
of married to your Bridget.
Face it, you're not ready
to be dating yet.
You want your ring back?
Yeah.
I don't need this anymore.
You sure?
I'm positive.
My precious! My precious!
My precious!
Mind if I take this?
Oh, uh, no--
somebody's sitting there.
Well, where are they?
They're not here yet.
Well, I'm here
and I need a chair.
No, uh...
honestly, I have a girl coming.
Well, when she gets here,
I'll give it back to her.
See, I don't believe that.
You calling me a liar?
No, but I've been burnt before.
I'm taking this chair.
No, you're not.
Yes, I am. Let go!
You let go
of the chair.
I had the chair before
you even came into the place.
- It's mine now!
- It's my chair now!
Walden, is everything all right?
Ha! She's here.
Now back off!
What was that all about?
It was an attempt
at a chairjacking.
Here, I get you a tea.
Thank you.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I'm trying to get my daughter
into Bellwood Academy.
It's a nightmare.
She tests well, but she did
not give a good interview.
How old is
your daughter again?
Five.
And Bellwood Academy is a...?
Kindergarten.
Wow, when I was five,
I got kicked out of preschool
for biting my teacher.
Why did you bite her?
She tried to steal my chair.
Yeah, you heard me! I bit her!
She had to get a shot!
Take it easy, okay?
So I was rather surprised
to hear from you.
What's up?
I was thinking a lot about what
you said about not wanting
to date me while I was
still, you know,
emotionally attached
to my ex-wife.
I said you were still
hopelessly in love with her.
Potato, Po-tah-to.
The point is you were right.
I wasn't ready to start
dating, but I am now.
A whole week later.
I understand your skepticism.
Which is why I want you to
witness what I'm about to do.
These...
are my final divorce papers.
And once I sign them, my
marriage will be over forever.
I was hoping that you
and I could start fresh.
Nothing like starting off
a new relationship
on the ashes of the old one.
That's what I was thinking.
Oh, uh, you got a pen?
Uh, I don't think I do.
Okay.
Uh, does anybody got a pen
I can borrow?
Anyone? Nobody?
Excuse me.
Do you got a pen?
Sorry.
It's unbelievable.
Oh, man.
Can I please borrow your pen?
I'm sorry, someone's using it.
Who?
They're not here yet.
I will give you a hundred
dollars to borrow that pen.
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Men, men, manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh,
ooh-ohh, ooh-ooh... ♪
♪ Men, men, men, men, manly men,
men, men ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Men, men, men, manly men, men, men ♪
♪ Ah. ♪
♪ Men. ♪
♪ Two and a Half Men 9x11 ♪
What a Lovely Landing Strip
Original Air Date on December 21, 2011
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
Jolly good sunset, eh, what?
Excuse me?
I like the way you talk,
so I thought
I'd give it a go.
Well, no one says "jolly good"
unless they're appearing in
a revival of Oliver.
Right, right, right, right,
right, right.
Please, sir,
may I have a kiss?
Stop it!
No, seriously, I want a kiss.
All right.
- Mm. So...
- Hmm?
would you like to stay
for dinner tonight?
Oh, I'd love to, but I have
to pick up my daughter.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
- How about dinner this weekend?
- Sure.
Great.
You like Mexican food?
I do.
Ooh, terrific.
So we'll go to Guadalajara.
Oh, that a new
restaurant?
No, it's an old city in Mexico.
You want to go to
Mexico for dinner?
Yep. We'll take my plane.
I'll have you back
by midnight.
So, hang on--
you-you don't own a pen,
but you own a plane?
Yeah, you can
always borrow a pen.
Try to borrow a plane.
- So...
- Mm?
what do you say?
Hmm... Let me see if
I can get a sitter.
Oh!
Yay!
- Mm-hmm.
- You know, I think we should
start making plans
for Christmas.
We can go surfing in Fiji,
skiing in the Alps,
making out in Malibu.
Yes, now, Walden,
let's be very clear:
You are a sweet and
wonderful guy,
but you've just come out
of a very long-term relationship,
- Sweet and wonderful.
so you're clearly on
the rebound.
Uh-huh. So?
Yes. So I don't know
if we should be making
Christmas plans just yet.
- Okay.
- Hmm?
Fine.
We'll slow things down.
Good.
Forget Christmas.
Thank you.
You'll be my Valentine,
though, right?
Oh, my God.
You're like no man
I've ever met.
Mmm! A bit of an
odd bloke, eh, what?
Oh, God, stop it.
Nudge, nudge, wink, wink,
say no more.
This is nice.
Like old times.
How so?
You and me, sitting
here, watching TV
while the good-looking
owner of the house is
out on the deck swapping
spit with a hot chick.
Yeah, there is
a bit of deja vu.
Not only that.
It feels like it's
happened before.
Yes, it does.
Man, I've seen so much
crazy stuff in this house,
I could write a book.
That's a good idea.
Got a title?
Hmm...
Maybe I can't
write a book.
All right then, cheerio!
Cheerio?
Means "good-bye"
in England.
Oh.
What do they have for
breakfast over there,
a bowl of good-byes?
- 'Ello, lads.
- Well, hey.
So, Zoey seems very nice.
Yeah, the bird really tickles
my fancy.
Help me out here.
Is "fancy" the English
word for "nutsack"?
No, it means that I like her.
I think this could get serious.
Wow, you're moving pretty quick,
aren't you?
That's what she said.
What are you laughing at?
He did a "That's what
she said" joke.
Because that's what she said.
Oh. That's not funny.
She thinks I'm on the rebound.
Well, aren't you?
You were with Bridget
for 15 years.
That's over.
I signed the divorce papers.
I'm ready to fall in love again.
Please tell me you didn't
actually say that to her.
Why?
Dude, even I know that's wrong.
Walden, you're young,
you're rich, you're handsome.
If I was even one
of those things
I would have screwed myself
to death years ago.
Well, I want to be in
a relationship...
with romance and intimacy
and commitment.
Oh, I get it. You're a chick.
Jake, we're living in
his house.
A very nice chick.
This is absolutely
ridiculous.
You don't have to wear the hat
if you don't want to.
It's not the hat.
Well, it's not totally the hat.
It's the incredible
extravagance.
You do realize I'm still not
ready to sleep with you, yes?
Oh, I'm not trying
to have sex with you.
Why not?
What's wrong with me?
Nothing. Why? Do you want
to have sex with me?
Yeah! No! No, it's too soon.
It's too soon.
Well, is it too soon...
for this?
Oh, God, Walden,
what have you done?
What do you think?
I think you're out
of your bloody mind.
I can't accept this.
Why not?
Because it's too much.
It's crazy!
What about getting a diamond
necklace for a girl
you've haven't slept with yet
while flying to Mexico
for dinner
on your private jet is crazy?
Okay, when I say it out loud
it does sound a little crazy.
Good thing I didn't get you
the matching tiara.
Okay, uh, there might be
one other thing.
Oh, God, you didn't buy me
a pony, did you?
No. Why, do you want one?
No, I don't.
The thing is, I know some people
on the board
of the private school
you're trying to get
your daughter in,
so I pulled some strings
and got her enrolled.
Wait-- you got Ava
into Bellwood?
But don't worry, one phone call
and she's out on her ass.
No, don't do that!
Walden, this is wonderful!
You're not upset?
No! No, no, no.
What you did is brilliant.
Mm!
Utterly brilliant.
Mr. Schmidt, we'll be descending
into Guadalajara in
a few minutes.
Circle, circle!
Excuse me?
He's about to descend
into London.
Hello, Heathrow!
Oh, God, that is
not funny.
What a lovely
landing strip.
♪ Men. ♪
- Morning.
Want to explain
the hat?
It's not a hat, it's a sombrero.
"Sombrero" is Spanish for "hat""
Really?
Seems awfully complicated.
Why don't they
just call it a hat?
No, not worth it.
- Morning.
Cameron Diaz, señor.
- Cameron Diaz?
- Choose your battles.
Right.
So, how'd it go last night?
It was great.
I think I'm falling in love.
Oh, Walden, that's
muy grande chiquita.
Hey, man...
I really don't appreciate
you making fun of me.
Sorry.
I'll get it.
Who knew he spoke Spanish?
♪ Zoey, Zoey,
Zoey, Zoe, Zoey... ♪
Bridget.
I can't sign the divorce papers.
I love you and I want you back.
Oh, bollocks.
♪ Men. ♪
Wait... whoa, whoa,
wait, I...
I don't understand.
You're the one who
wanted the divorce.
I know-- I thought
it's what I wanted,
but when I saw your name
on the papers,
I just, I couldn't sign.
Ay, Chihuahua.
Stop it.
Sorry, it's the hat.
Is everything okay?
You don't look happy.
Yeah, no, yeah,
it's great.
I just...
What about that doctor
you were dating?
Alex?
I saw him.
He's a dreamboat.
The truth is, he was
just a rebound thing.
Yeah, but rebounds
work out sometimes.
I mean, take Abe Lincoln.
He met his wife on a rebound,
and, and they had a
long-term relationship.
Until, you know...
Hm... I didn't know
Abe Lincoln killed himself.
How many rebounds have you
had since we broke up?
Well...
It's a trap, don't answer.
None that meant anything.
Yes!
I mean, I haven't
exactly been celibate.
- Oh, no, no, no, no, no!
- But I haven't been a slut, either.
Attaboy.
Come on, let's go upstairs.
- Really?
- Don't you want to?
Well, yeah, I want to.
I just, I-I...shouldn't
we be taking it slow?
We've been married
for 15 years, Walden.
Come on.
Okay.
- Hello.
- Hey.
Hi.
It's very weird that you
live with these people.
So what's he gonna
do about Zoey?
Well, unless I miss my guess,
he's gonna lie to both of them
until it blows up in his face,
and everyone gets
their feelings hurt,
and he's left alone
and miserable.
Wow. That sucks.
Isn't there a better way to
date two women
at the same time?
Aw, Jake...
No.
I want you so badly.
Yeah, yep, I, uh...
...want you too.
I was such a fool.
I can't believe I let someone
as great as you get away.
Wait, you said I was immature.
You are, but that's
part of your charm.
I love you, Walden.
I love you, I love you,
I love you.
That is awesome.
Uh...
Just... okay,
okay, well...
Can we just hold on
for one second?
- Where are you going?
- Uh, the bathroom.
Why don't you just use that one?
I'm a little pee shy.
I don't want you to hear me.
Since when?
It's a new thing.
People change, Bridget,
people grow.
Do you think you and Mom
would ever get back together?
Well, you know I will always
care for your mother.
She's a terrific lady,
and a great mom,
and no one can predict
the future...
but no freakin' way.
She said the same thing.
But used a different word
than "freakin'."
- Hey.
Hey.
Everything all right?
Uh, no. As Zoey would say,
I'm in a bit of a sticky wicket.
You mean you were
in a sticky wicket,
then you finished up and
came down here for a snack.
No, no, I-I have a conundrum.
Then you should've worn it.
Might've avoided the stickiness,
you know, wicket-wise.
Okay, I'm just going
to talk to you.
Please.
I've been dreaming about getting
back together with Bridget
for months now, but since
I met Zoey, I'm not so sure.
- It is a pickle.
- What's a pickle?
Shh.
What does your heart tell you?
My heart tells me that
Bridget is the past,
and Zoey is the future.
Oh, I get it.
You're trying to figure out
which one gets your pickle.
Essentially, yes.
Well, then, I say
follow your heart.
I say follow your pickle.
Try to ignore him.
I've been with Bridget
for 15 years.
That's tough to
just walk away from.
But as you said yourself,
Bridget's the past.
Yeah, but if I get
back together with her,
I don't have to
give up $600 million
in a divorce settlement.
The future's overrated.
Go with Bridget.
I mean, it does make sense,
right? All I'd have to do
is sell this place
and move back in with her.
You can't live your
life in the past.
- Go with Zoey.
- You think?
I do. And I don't have
a horse in this race.
No, you're right.
Zoey it is.
Thank you, Alan.
Cheerios!
You have no shame, do you?
Shame, no.
Malibu beach house, yes.
Welcome back.
Oh, boy.
Bridget, I can't remember--
do you like your Band-Aids
taken off quick or slow?
I don't understand.
Let's just go with quick.
I don't think it's a good
idea to sleep with you,
since I started
seeing someone new
and I think she might
be the real deal.
Not that you weren't
the real deal,
you're just the ex-real deal,
and she's the next real deal.
Anyway, I'd like for you you to
sign the divorce papers,
so we can both go meet
people we like better.
- What?
- Friends?
- I am so humiliated!
- I'm sorry!
I can't believe you waited till
I was half naked in your bed
to tell me you were
seeing someone else!
Kind of hard to bring up while
you're taking off my pants.
And by the way,
you look sensational.
The Pilates is
really paying off.
Go to hell,
you son of a bitch!
How about an "attaboy" for not
having sex with you out of
respect for the other woman
I'm falling in love with?
Drop dead!
How many times have
we seen this movie?
Too many to count.
Maybe it's the house.
- What do you mean?
- I think it's haunted.
Like, built on an angry
woman burial ground.
Certainly can't be the fault
of the men who live in it.
Sometimes at night,
if I'm really quiet,
I think I can hear
them bitching.
That didn't go as well
as I'd hoped.
I wouldn't worry about it.
She doesn't look like
the type to carry a grudge.
But I don't know her
like you do.
Haunted...
♪ Men. ♪
So the madam
of the brothel opens the door
and there's a man on the stoop
with no arms and no legs.
And she says, "What do you think
you're going to do here?"
And he says,
"I rang the bell, didn't I?"
You're terrible.
Did he break your heart?
Who are you?
That doesn't matter.
Do you want him back, or
do you want him to suffer?
I don't know.
That's all right.
Oftentimes,
they're the same thing.
Come with me,
and I'll teach you.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==